{
  "datas" : [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which word start with 'a'",
        "options": ["orange", "apple", "strawberry", "cow"],
        "answer": "apple"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which word start with 'g'",
        "options": ["orange", "blue", "yellow", "green"],
        "answer": "green"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which word start with 'r'",
        "options": ["red", "green", "blue", "purple"],
        "answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which word start with 'b'",
      "options": ["red", "green", "blue", "purple"],
      "answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which word start with 'p'",
      "options": ["red", "green", "blue", "purple"],
      "answer": "purple"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which word start with 's'",
      "options": ["red", "gray", "skyblue", "purple"],
      "answer": "skyblue"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which word start with 'w'",
      "options": ["red", "white", "blue", "purple"],
      "answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which word start with 'i'",
      "options": ["ice", "green", "blue", "purple"],
      "answer": "ice"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which word start with 'vesion'",
      "options": ["vesion", "green", "blue", "purple"],
      "answer": "vesion"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which word start with 'f'",
      "options": ["fast", "green", "blue", "purple"],
      "answer": "fast"
    }
  ]
} 